[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
So we've now built a simple scatter plot and
到现在我们做了一个简单的散点图
we get an idea of what our data looks like.
我们对数据有了大体的印象
And the question is,
那么问题是
can we use the scatter plot to predict sales price from square feet of living?
我们能不能用散点图来通过房屋面积预测价格
So we're gonna do a simple regression model.
所以我们来建立一个简单的回归模型
So let's do that, and we hit SM, and
让我们做一下 我们点击SM
we're gonna say #Create a simple
然后我们写道 #建立一个
regression model of sqft_living to price.
房屋面积与价格的简单回归模型
All right, so let's do just that.
好 让我们来实现
So remember from the lectures that the first thing that you do before you do
从这一课你们就要记住 在你们对
anything to your data is to split it into a training set and a test set,
数据做任何处理之前 都要先把它分为训练集和测试集
because you never want to do, trying training or
因为你从来不会 把训练和学习的处理
learning on the test data, you want to do that just on the training data.
放在测试数据上 你只会把这些用在训练集中的数据
So let's do that, split, so I'm gonna take my data and
让我们来做分离的工作 我准备把我的数据
split it into train_data and test_data by calling
分为训练集和测试集
a function that's called, that you can apply to an so
通过调用一个函数
it's called the random split function.
我们把它称为随机分布函数
Sales.random_split.
Sales.random_split
By the way, what I did there was just use tab complete.
顺便 我刚刚使用了tab来自动补全
So let me just show you that little trick, just for a second.
让我教你们一个小技巧 就几秒
So if I just do sales.r and I press Tab,
当我写到 sale.r 然后敲一下tab键
you'll see there's a few things I could do.
你会看到有很多能完成的命令
random_split, read_csv, remove_columns, rename_columns and so on.
random_split, read_csv, remove_columns rename_columns 还有很多
So I'm gonna just do random_split.
于是我选择random_split
And what I'm gonna tell it is to do a .8 split.
接下来我要做的是a.8.split
So .8 of the data, 80% is gonna be for training and 20% is gonna be for testing.
.8意味着数据中的80%将作为训练集 20%将作为测试集
Now, one last thing that will be useful for your homeworks and in general,
最后一件你会在作业或整个课程中用到的
to make sure that you have always the same results is to set a seed for the split.
就是确保你总是得到同样的结果 你需要为分布函数设一个随机种子
Because a random split, it's a pseudo random number generator.
因为随机分布 并不是真正意义上的随机数产生器 而是伪随机数产生器
We can set a seed to it, and we just gonna set the seed to be any number we want.
我们需要给它一个种子 我们可以把这个种子设为任一个数
For example, it could be 2015,
例如 我把它设为2015
it could be many things, so I'm just gonna set it to 0.
它还可以是其它任何数 我可以将它设为0
So now every time I do this random split, it splits the data in the same way.
现在每次做随机分布 它会用同样的方式分离数据
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community